export const homepageMockdata = [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "What is WordPress?",
        answer: (
          <>
          <p>It is the most common Content Management System in the world. It is easy to use for the creation of website software in the world. It provides everything you need to create a website according to what you want within your budget. You can install WordPress directly on the MadPopo server. It is the open-source & based on the programming of PHP concepts.</p>
          <p>The best part about WordPress is that it has potential and you can fit almost in any project, It is easy to learn at the same time. It has many options like the wealth of themes, add-ons, and plugins that must be easily installed as required by you for making your project with endless options for customization.</p> 
          <p>MadPopo makes it's easy to buy in your budget with all features with 24 by 7 customer support.</p>
          </>
        )
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "What kind of website can I create on WordPress?",
        answer:
          "WordPress is widely diverse as you can make any of these types of work like e-commerce, blog, affiliate website, digital marketing & etc. Wordpress is the best web presence among the choices anywhere in the world."
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Is your WordPress version different from WordPress.org version?",
        answer:
          "You no need to worry about the updates with MadPopo as we enable automatic update features, auto-installer that will make sure that your website is always worked on latest plugins, tech & etc, You can make without limits & install all the themes or plugins you to make your project awesome."
      },
      {
        id: "4",
        question: "How WordPress hosting is different from regular web hosting?",
        answer:(
          <>
          <p>WordPress has many resources, many custom tools, plugins that optimise your WordPress hosting experience, Wordpress also has features like WP-CLI, GIT and SSH.</p>
          <p>WordPress hosting is for you, take the chance and get started to use our auto-installer tool and begin your project! Once you start then you can take advantage of pre-installed caching plugins and it has many other features that will increase your speed and performance of your website to the next level.</p>
          </>
        )
      },
      {
        id: "5",
        question: "How to get started after purchasing WordPress hosting from MadPopo?",
        answer:
          "When you have purchased now you have to go to our control panel, choose the WordPress option on our auto-installer and log into your WordPress panel once the installation is complete! Logging in is as simple as going to a dedicated URL like www.exampledomain.(.com/.in/etc)/wp-admin."
      },
      {
        id: "6",
        question: "Can I transfer my WordPress website that is hosted with a different provider to MadPopo?",
        answer:(
          <>
          <p>Yes, we have made the process very easy than most other hosting providers. Your WordPress website can be moved over in a single click.</p>
          <p>Any issue arises we will solve it & customer support team with 24/7/365."</p>
          </>
        )
      },
      {
        id: "7",
        question: "Is MadPopo secure enough to host WordPress?",
        answer:(
          <>
          <p>You can't call yourself a great web hosting provider if you don't take security seriously! That's why we invest more money in security solutions. The infrastructure provided by us to make sure that the use of collective intelligence makes all servers entirely secure.</p>
          <p>We also make web honeypots and other features that guarantee defence against potentially fatal attacks. You can sleep easy, knowing that you're safe with MadPopo.</p>
          </>
        )
      },
    ];
    
export const wordpressHostingData = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "WordPress Hosting: What Is It?",
    answer:
      "WordPress hosting is a type of web hosting that is specifically optimized for running WordPress websites. WordPress is a popular content management system (CMS) that powers millions of websites worldwide. WordPress hosting typically includes a set of features and resources that are designed to optimize the performance, security, and reliability of WordPress websites."
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "What are the advantages of WordPress Hosting?",
    answer:(
      <>
      <p>WordPress hosting has a number of benefits, including:</p>
      <p>Simple setup and administration: Since WordPress hosting is created expressly to host WordPress websites, the setup procedure is frequently streamlined and user-friendly. WordPress can often be installed with only one click through a number of hosting companies, making it simple for customers to launch their website.</p>
      <p>Performance optimisation: WordPress hosting has been specifically created to meet the needs of WordPress, which means that it is best suited for hosting WordPress websites. This may lead to quicker loading times and an improved user experience in general.</p>
      </>
    )
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question: "How Do I Choose the Right WordPress Hosting Plan?",
    answer:
      "The resources allotted and available in the various MadPopo WordPress hosting plans vary. We propose our StarterBoost plan for regularly occurring sites that are just getting started, sites that do not keep a sizable database, and/or sites that do not receive a lot of traffic. You might want to take a look at our GeekPro plan for websites that are actively gaining more visitors."
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "Who Needs WordPress Hosting?",
    answer:(
      <>
      <p>WordPress hosting is a great choice for anyone who wants to build and run a WordPress website. This includes individuals, bloggers, small businesses, and even large corporations. If you're planning to build a website using WordPress, then WordPress hosting is the ideal hosting solution for you.</p>
      <p>WordPress hosting is distinct from other types of hosting since it is created to fulfill the particular needs of WordPress websites. WordPress hosting might not be the ideal choice for you if you use a different content management system (CMS).</p>
      <p>In general, WordPress hosting is the best hosting option for you if you intend to develop a website using the CMS.</p>
      </>
    )
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: "How Come MadPopo For WordPress?",
    answer:
      "One of the best WordPress hosting companies, MadPopo, comes highly recommended by WordPress.org. With an extensive array of services and solutions created exclusively for WordPress, the company has established a solid reputation for providing outstanding 24/7 customer care and support. There are a tonne of performance and security features with regular additions and improvements, in addition to its robust and blazing-fast hosting platform that makes use of the ground-breaking Google Cloud infrastructure."
  },
]

export const wooCommerceData = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "What is managed WooCommerce hosting?",
    answer:
      "In managed WooCommerce hosting, a client leases a dedicated server rather than sharing one. Additional services are also provided, including improved security and support."
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "How do WooCommerce hosting and WordPress hosting differ from one another?",
    answer:
      "The performance needs are where WooCommerce and WordPress hosting diverge most. Due to the unique performance needs that stores employing WooCommerce have, not all WordPress hosting plans are optimized for it."
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question: "Between Shopify and WooCommerce, I'm not sure which to pick. Help, please?",
    answer:
      "Both Shopify and WooCommerce are popular e-commerce platforms that offer unique features and benefits. The choice between the two ultimately depends on your specific needs and preferences."
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "What is the cost of using WooCommerce?",
    answer:
      "According to your unique demands and preferences, using WooCommerce might range greatly in price. However, a lot of online store owners discover that setting up and maintaining an e-commerce website with WooCommerce is affordable."
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: "Does WooCommerce need the installation of WordPress?",
    answer:
      "Yes, WooCommerce is a plugin that needs WordPress to be installed on your website in order to work. WordPress is a content management system (CMS) that offers the foundation for your website and enables you to generate and manage all of the material on it."
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "For WooCommerce, do you offer backups?",
    answer:
      "Automatic backups for WooCommerce stores are enabled by default on all of our servers. However, you can even manage the backup frequency and set it to as regularly as 1 backup every hour."
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: "Do free SSL certificates come with WooCommerce?",
    answer:
      "For enhanced security and data protection on your WooCommerce stores, yes, our quick WooCommerce website hosting includes free SSL certificates by Let's Encrypt."
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: "DAdding team members to manage my WooCommerce store is possible.",
    answer:
      "Yes! You may add team members and give them full or limited access to your WooCommerce servers and stores with our Team Collaboration feature."
  },
]

export const linuxHostingMockdata = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "What is Linux hosting?",
    answer:(
      <>
      <p>A type of web hosting known as "Linux hosting" makes use of the Linux operating system as the foundation of the server. Due to its reliability, security, and flexibility, Linux, a well-known open-source operating system, is frequently used for web servers. Popular online programming languages including PHP, Perl, Python, and Ruby are supported by Linux hosting, which commonly employs Apache as the web server software.</p>
      </>
    )
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "What are the benefits of Linux hosting?",
    answer:
      "Hosting on Linux has a number of advantages, including open-source, stability, dependability, security, flexibility, compatibility, and scalability. Overall, Linux hosting is a dependable, safe, and budget-friendly option for companies and private individuals who wish to host their websites on a solid and adaptable platform."
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question: "Can I host my Windows-created website on a Linux webserver?",
    answer:
      "Yes, it is feasible to host a Windows-based website on a Linux web server. However, if your website makes use of Windows-specific tools or technologies like ASP.NET or Microsoft SQL Server, you might run into compatibility problems. In such circumstances, you might need to alter or completely rewrite your website in order to make it work on the Linux platform."
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "Why is MadPopo the top Linux shared hosting provider?",
    answer:
      "MadPopo is a top Linux hosting provider due to its cost-effective and feature-rich unmetered hosting options suitable for businesses of all sizes. Our high-performance hosting services cater to startups, and medium and large businesses with ease, helping them save time and money."
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: "I already have a domain name registered with another registrar. Can I host it on a Linux server?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you can host a domain name that is already registered by ordering it online or through our sales team. All domain extensions available on the market can be effortlessly hosted on our Linux server."
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "Do I need a domain name from MadPopo in order to purchase web hosting?",
    answer:
      "No, you can use your existing domain name or purchase a new one from any provider to use MadPopo's web hosting services. There is no requirement to purchase a domain name from us to use our hosting services."
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: "Will shared web hosting works smoother for my website too?",
    answer:
      "Linux hosting has gained much popularity among businesses as they have found a much cheaper and reliable alternative in the field of cheap Linux hosting India. MadPopo has generated a niche for itself in the market with affordable hosting plans and set a standard to be followed by others."
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: "Does the Starter Linux hosting plan allow for a separate cPanel?",
    answer:
      "Yes, the Starter Linux hosting plan comes with the best control panel, cPanel, to manage files, emails, databases, and more."
  },
]

export const windowsHostingMockdata = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "What is the purpose of Windows web hosting?",
    answer:(
      <>
      <p>Web hosting that employs the Windows operating system as the hosting platform is known as "Windows web hosting". This kind of hosting is specifically made to handle websites and programs that use Windows-based technologies like ASP.NET, MSSQL, or Visual Basic."</p>
      </>
    )
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "Is it possible for me to build and resell various packages under my Windows web hosting package?",
    answer:
      "You can create a number of hosting packages under your Windows web hosting account in order to resell hosting services to other people. This technique, known as reseller hosting, allows you to set up and manage many hosting accounts under your primary account."
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question: "On a Windows web hosting plan, how many websites can I host?",
    answer:
      "Depending on the hosting company and the particular plan you select, the number of websites you can host on a Windows web hosting package. The number of websites you can host with some hosting services may be restricted by the resources allotted to your account, whereas unlimited websites may be available with other hosting providers."
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "On Windows web hosting, which databases are supported?",
    answer:
      "Microsoft SQL Server and MySQL databases are just two of the many databases that are supported by Windows web hosting. Make sure the Windows web hosting plan supports the database system you require for your website or application when making your selection. In order to make sure that your hosting package can accommodate your database needs, you need also to take other aspects into account, such as disc space, bandwidth, and processor power."
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: "Why should I host my website on a shared Windows platform?",
    answer:
      "If you need to use Microsoft technologies, want an easy-to-use hosting solution, are looking for an affordable hosting option, need a stable and secure hosting environment, or need scalability to accommodate future growth, hosting your website on a shared Windows platform can be a good choice. To make sure that the plan you choose satisfies your particular needs, you should thoroughly study the features and restrictions of the hosting company you select."
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "Why is Windows hosting so powerful?",
    answer:
      "The reason why Windows hosting is effective is because it was created especially for the Windows operating system, which is renowned for its reliability, security, and performance. For a hosting plan that runs on Windows, each of these elements is crucial. That is why we have such faith in the quality of our offerings. In addition to offering tools with our Windows web hosting plans to keep your website functioning properly, we also offer featured-pack tools to help your online business succeed."
  },
]